How's Jimmy today?
Jimmy今天怎么样了?
Better. Thank you, Doctor.
他好些了. 谢谢您, 医生.
Can I see him please, Mrs. Williams?
我可以看看他吗, Williams夫人?
Certainly, doctor.
当然可以, 医生.
Come upstairs.
上楼吧.
You look very well, Jimmy.
你看上去很好, Jimmy.
You are better now,
你现在好些了,
but you mustn't get up yet.
但你还不应该起床.
The boy mustn't go to school yet, Mrs. Williams.
这孩子还不能去上学, Williams夫人，
And he mustn't eat rich food.
而且不能吃油腻的食物.
Does he have a temperature, doctor?
他还发烧吗, 医生?
No, he doesn't.
不, 他不发烧了.
Must he stay in bed?
他还必须卧床吗?
Yes. He must remain in bed for another two days.
是的. 他还必须卧床两天.
He can get up for about two hours each day,
他每天可以起来两个小时,
but you must keep the room warm.
但您必须保持房间温暖.
Where's Mr. Williams this evening?
Williams先生今晚去哪儿了?
He's in bed, doctor.
他在床上呢, 医生.
Can you see him please?
您能看看他吗?
He has a bad cold, too!
他也得了重感冒!